{
    "subject": "resource/Petroglyph_Games",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Petroglyph Games is located in the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9839932322502136,
            "question": "Is Petroglyph Games based in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9492607712745667,
            "question": "Where is Petroglyph Games located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8515514731407166,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of Petroglyph Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8336145877838135,
            "question": "Is Petroglyph Games a US-based company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8036237359046936,
            "question": "Where can you find the headquarters of Petroglyph Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7906907796859741,
            "question": "In what part of the world is Petroglyph Games situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7408798336982727,
            "question": "In which nation does Petroglyph Games operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6485943794250488,
            "question": "To which country does Petroglyph Games belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5982394218444824,
            "question": "What country is home to Petroglyph Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5129398107528687,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Petroglyph Games?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Petroglyph Games is located in the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7181_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is home to Petroglyph Games?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7181_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Petroglyph Games belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7181_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which nation does Petroglyph Games operate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7181_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7181_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Petroglyph Games is located in the United States. This can be inferred from the following statements:\n\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7181/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt contains the phrase \"2003\u2022Las Vegas (United States )\u2022Unfunded\", which indicates that Petroglyph is based in Las Vegas, USA.\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7181/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt contains the phrase \"Petroglyph Games...based in Las Vegas, Nevada, United States\", which further confirms that Petroglyph is located in the United States.\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7181/re-ranker-msmarco/54.txt contains a statement that says \"Petroglyph Games is an independent game developer based in Las Vegas, Nevada\", which also indicates that Petroglyph is located in the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Petroglyph Games is based in Las Vegas, Nevada, which is in the United States. Therefore, the statement \"Petroglyph Games is located in the United States\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}